/*
   4 Nisan 2023 Salı20:22:12
   User: 
   Server: (localdb)\MSSQLLocalDB
   Database: P013Db
   Application: 
*/

'Kullanicilar' table
- Unable to create index 'UQ_KullaniciTC'.  
The CREATE UNIQUE INDEX statement terminated because a duplicate key was found for the object name 'dbo.Kullanicilar' and the index name 'UQ_KullaniciTC'. The duplicate key value is (123456789  ).
Could not create constraint or index. See previous errors.
The statement has been terminated.

